Flat Justice Privacy Policy

Updated 31/12/2019

Our Promise To You

Flat Justice Community Interest Company Ltd. is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy.This privacy policy statement is to make you aware of our how we protect personal data.

We’ve designed our website www.GetRentBack.org so that you can visit without having to register orprovide us with any personal information: we want you to benefit from our free information resourceon tenant rights and Rent Repayment Orders.

If you choose to provide us with any personal information, you can be sure it will only be used tosupport your relationship with Flat Justice and to help us provide you with relevant information. Thisapplies regardless of whether you contact us by phone, email or post.

As a not-for-profit organisation we are not required to register with the Information Commissioner'sOffice.

Flat Justice Community Interest Company Ltd, Company Number 11502292, is a registered not-for-profitcompany in England and Wales. The registered address is 1st Floor 85 Great Portland Street, LondonW1W 7LT.

Data Collection

There is no requirement to provide us with any personal information if you want to use the free onlineinformation resource on our website.

Although using cookies helps us to improve our site, you do not need to accept our cookies in order toaccess our website. The majority of web browsers allow some control of cookies.

If you decide to contact Flat Justice, we will only collect sufficient information about you to allow us todeal with your query and communicate with you in an appropriate way. We try and keep any suchinformation to a minimum.

Specifically, we may use your information to communicate with you, respond to your query or provideyou with our support.

Flat Justice will never sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others.

If we are representing you in a Rent Repayment Order Application, we will need to hold moreinformation about you to enable us to deal effectively with your request.

For our billing system, we record a client’s name, business name (if any), postal address, email addressand contact telephone number(s).

We will never store client credit or debit card details and only accept payment for the services weprovide by BACS transfer or cheque.

All information and supporting documentation that you share with us will be held securely and willnever by disclosed to a third party without your prior written agreement: for example, if you ask us tosubmit a Rent Repayment Order Application on your behalf or if you ask us to liaise with a third party onyour behalf. Data collection, processing and storage may involve third parties which we have verified tothe best of our ability as being GDPR compliant.

Subject access requests

Flat Justice recognises that individuals have the right to access their personal data and can make arequest verbally or in writing. If we receive a subject access request asking what information is heldabout them, we will deal with the request without undue delay and at the latest within one month ofreceipt.

If the request is particularly complex, we reserve the right to extend this timescale by a further twomonths.

We may need to confirm the identity of the applicant before releasing personal information to them.After all, we want to protect your privacy.

In most cases, the subject access request will be handled at no cost to the applicant. If the request ismanifestly unfounded or excessive, we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for theadministrative costs of complying with the request.

Security

Flat Justice is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorised access ordisclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in placeappropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information wecollect online, by email, phone or through information you send us by post.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please email us at office@flatjustice.org or write tous at:

Flat Justice Community Interest Company,

1st Floor, 85 Great Portland Street,

London

W1W 7LT
